始祖家族   第一季 第三集
本字幕由YYeTs人人影视 原创翻译制作
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
美剧字幕下载 请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
翻译：胖兔纯    树树    Alexy    茶炒栗子    米苏
时间轴：今    Ans    MH      校对：米苏
后期：渔夫      字幕总监制：米苏
我的哥哥们和我都是历史上
My brothers and I are the first vampires,
最早的吸血鬼  是始祖家族
in all of history-- the originals.
三百年前  我们帮助建立了新奥尔良
300 years ago, we helped build New Orleans.
现在我们回到了这个战争中的城市
Now we've returned to find a city at war.
吸血鬼马塞尔领导着一支部队
The vampire Marcel leads an army
对抗一群绝望的女巫
against a coven of desperate witches.
我的哥哥克劳斯与他们两者为敌
My brother Klaus is playing against both sides,
他渴望权力
hungry for power
希望保护怀着他孩子的狼人
and hoping to protect the werewolf carrying his child,
但是马塞尔有一个优势
but Marcel has an advantage.
他在一个秘密武器的帮助下
He holds our brother Elijah captive
俘获了我们的哥哥以利亚
with the aid of a secret weapon.
现在为了救回我深爱的哥哥
Now in order to get back the brother I love,
我别无选择
I have no choice
只能支持我无法信任的那个哥哥
but to side with the one I cannot trust.
1359年8月
August 1359.
我注意到兄弟姐妹之间的一个不同
I have noticed a difference in my siblings.
我们之间的联系
Our bond strains
在吸血鬼生活的压力之下更为紧张
beneath the pressure of our life as vampires.
一旦被吸血鬼的魔性缠身
Each day removes them further from the humanity
就会离人性日渐日远
they once possessed.
我亲爱的妹妹丽贝卡
My sweet sister Rebekah
变得越来越冷漠无情
has grown quite indifferent to brutality.
然而  问题最大的还是尼克劳斯
However, the true problem remains, my brother Niklaus.
他依然用残忍掩饰着自己的孤独
He continues to hide his loneliness with cruelty.
不过  我依然坚持相信  我作为他们的大哥
Still, I cling to the hope that I, as their eldest brother,
可以将他们领回正轨
can lead them down the correct path,
受到家族力量指引的正轨
a path charged with the power of a family united...
如果我失败了
For if I fail,
我们的家族只能在黑暗中沦陷
our family's legacy will end in darkness.
我不敢相信
I cannot believe
你居然不等我  自己处理了那些吸血鬼
you disposed of those vampires without me.
我知道我最喜欢火烧一切了
You know how I love to set things on fire.
难道我该把他们留在前院任由他们腐烂吗
Was I supposed to leave them in the front yard to rot?
再说了  他们是我该负的责任
Besides, they were my responsibility.
他们攻击了怀着我孩子的
They attacked the helpless, pregnant girl
无助的小孕妇
who's carrying my child.
我好感动啊
Oh, I am so moved
你对怀着你的混血儿孩子的狼人的
by your newfound sense of fatherly duty
新生父亲的职责
towards the werewolf carrying
好让我感动
your hybrid bun in her oven.
狼女想知道计划是什么
The werewolf would like to know what the plan is.
那要看你说的是什么计划
Well, that depends what plan you mean, luv--
是我统治全球的计划
My plan for global domination
还是丽贝卡在残酷世界中寻找真爱的计划
or Rebekah's plan to find love in a cruel, cruel world.
营救以利亚的计划
The plan to rescue Elijah,
你知道  那个好哥哥
you know-- the good brother,
被你从背后插入匕首
the one who is now in the possession
现在被你的死敌
of your mortal enemy after you stabbed him
所控制的那个
in the back.
明确点说  是从前面
In the front, if we're being specific.
你们俩说过你们会救回他的
You two said that you would get him back.
那么现在有计划吗
So is there a plan, or what?
好吧
Ok.
首先  马塞尔不是我的死敌
Well, firstly, Marcel is not my mortal enemy.
他是我的朋友
He's my friend,
虽然他没有意识到
albeit one who is unaware
我正试图破坏
that I am trying to sabotage
他对整个超自然法属区的控制
his hold over the supernatural community of the french quarter,
但是尽管如此  还是朋友
but a friend nonetheless,
第二点  我用匕首封住以利亚
and secondly, I daggered Elijah
是为了赢得马塞尔的信任
in order to gain Marcel's trust.
要是我早知道
If I had known
他会让我的哥哥被一个
he would place my brother in the hands of
特别暴躁的十几岁的巫师控制
a particularly nasty teenage witch,
我绝对会考虑做出略微不同的选择
I certainly would have weighed my options a bit differently,
第三点  妹妹  请说
and thirdly, sister, please.
第三点  正如你所要求的
And thirdly, the plan, as you have demanded,
计划就是尼克劳斯直接向马塞尔要回以利亚
is for Niklaus to simply asks Marcel for Elijah back.
这并不是全部的计划  是吗
That's not the whole plan, is it?
拜托
Oh, please.
克劳斯也许作为一个兄弟并不称职
Klaus may be a miserable excuse for a sibling,
但是没有别的坏心了
but there is none more diabolical.
这就是唯一的计划  亲爱的
That's only the plan "A," luv.
但总有备用计划
There's always a plan "B."
备用计划是什么
And what's plan "B"?
开战
War.
讨厌  我穿西装太帅了
Damn, I do look good in a suit.
即时新闻
游客失踪
约书亚·罗森  18岁
Joshua Rosen, 18,
近日来到新奥尔良  作为...
had recently arrived in New Orleans as part of...
我在码头的手下会主动站出来
My guy at the docks is gonna come forward
做目击证人
as an eyewitness,
证明他看到
say he saw
这两个喝醉了的人摔进了密西西比河
those two drunkenly fall into the Mississippi.
他们会被调查好几周
They'll be dredging for weeks.
没人会到这附近察看
No one will come looking around here.
那很好
That's good,
考虑到一个死在了县停尸房后面的垃圾桶里
considering one is dead in a dumpster behind the county morgue
而另一个现在已经是吸血鬼了
and the other one is a vampire now.
还有什么吗
Anything else?
请让我来  亲爱的
Allow me, darling.
还有一件事
One thing.
我派出了4个夜行吸血鬼
I sent 4 nightwalkers
去调查法属区出现的一个狼人
to look into a werewolf sighting in the quarter.
之后就再也没有他们的消息了
I haven't heard from them since.
那上周一共死了10个夜行吸血鬼了
That makes 10 dead nightwalkers in the last week.
你觉得是狼人重新回到这里
You think the werewolves are back in town
想要制造麻烦吗
trying to start some trouble?
我知道你和克劳斯是朋友
Look. I know you and Klaus are friends,
但事实是  自从始祖们出现
but the fact is, since the originals showed up--
快住嘴吧  蒂埃里
Oh, come now, Thierry.
你不会还在为我之前给你的
You're not still upset about that
一小口有毒的狼人伤口而生气吧
little, toxic werewolf bite I gave you, are you?
我以为那已经是过去的恩怨了
I thought we were at bygones.
我看你现在也给了他在这片区域自由行动的特权
I see you've given him free rein of your compound now, too.
没错  就当做是我的家人和我
Yes. Well, seeing as my family and I
曾住在这里  建立了这地方  实际上
lived here, built the place, in fact--
行了  别这样
All right. Come on.
你们俩都知道规矩
You both know the drill.
蒂埃里是我的人  亲信
Thierry is my guy, inner circle.
克劳斯是我的旧友和忠主
Klaus is my old-time friend and sire.
还是这里的客人
He's also a guest here.
和平共处  行吗  行吗
Peace, all right? All right?
你有何需要  兄弟
What you need, my brother?
我想我妹妹丽贝卡坚持让我要回以利亚
I'm afraid my sister Rebekah is insisting I demand Elijah's return.
她对此非常生气
She's quite worked up about it.
当然
I'll say.
马上就要有3个始祖在镇上活动了  是吗
We're not gonna have 3 originals walking around town, are we?
我们有一半人
Half our guys
都觉得是他妹妹杀死了夜行吸血鬼
think the sister killed the nightwalkers.
那是对一个始祖的指控吗
Is that an accusation against an original?
我刚刚不是说了要和平共处吗
What did I say about peace?
来
Come on.
跟我走走
Walk with me.
你的亲信缺乏幽默感
Your inner circle man lacks a sense of humor.
他有点过分保护我  但是十分忠诚
He's a little overprotective, but loyal to a fault.
在四十年代  我救了他
I saved his life back in the forties,
在退伍军人医院外发现他因战伤快要死掉
found him dying of a war wound outside a VA hospital.
他会为我杀人  为我而死
He'd kill for me and die for me.
还有  那个男孩吹小号真的好到不行
Plus, that boy can play the trumpet like you would not believe.
也许看看今晚能不能让他在派对上表演一下
Maybe I'll see if he can play a little tonight at the party.
你会来的  对吧
You're coming, right?
我怎么能错过认识议员的机会呢
How can I miss my chance to meet the city councilman
他可是接受了你们巨额的慈善捐款呢
as he accepts your gigantic charitable donation?
他是个笨蛋
Oh, he's a schmuck,
但是为了某些社区服务
but he lets us do our thing
他允许我们做自己的事情
in exchange for certain community services,
比如不把我们的尖牙对准当地人
like keeping our fangs out of the locals.
听着
Listen.
关于你哥哥
About your brother,
我很想帮你排忧解难  但是蒂埃里说得对
I would love to help you out, but Thierry is right.
我的人都紧张不安
My guys are on edge.
他们看到始祖家族回到这里
They see the original family moving in,
有吸血鬼死掉  这让他们非常紧张
vampires dying, it makes them nervous.
如果我现在把以利亚还给你
If I hand Elijah back now,
也许会产生错误印象
it might give the wrong impression
让他们不知道谁是这里真正的老大
about who's really in charge here.
你懂我意思嘛
You know what I mean?
你得理解我不得不开口
You understand I had to ask.
克劳斯  帮抹大拉的玛利亚[娼妓]问一句
Hey, Klaus, for the love of Mary Magdalene,
一个简单的问题要问多久
how long does it take to ask a simple question?
比你们想的要久多了
Much longer than you'd think,
因为回答正如预期中一样  是不行
considering the answer was, as expected, no.
马塞尔的手下  蒂埃里很多疑
Marcel's man Thierry is suspicious.
他绝对是你杀死了10个夜行吸血鬼
He thinks you killed 10 nightwalkers.
说谎  我只杀了8个
Well, that's a lie. I only killed 8.
我应该让蒂埃里成为第九个吗
Should I make Thierry the ninth?
马塞尔在假装友善
Marcel is playing friendly.
我们不能杀死他最爱的儿子
We can't kill the favorite son,
否则他会对付我们的
or he'll catch onto us.
-那就开战吧  -的确是
- So war it is, then. - Indeed.
你知道怎么对付那个女巫吗
Do you know what to do with the witch?
-我觉得知道  -很好
- I believe I do. - Good.
你对付索菲·德弗罗
You manage Sophie Deveraux.
我来负责下一步
I'll take care of the next step.
我命令你放干他的血
I ordered you to drain him of blood.
怎么这么久
What's taking so long?
抱歉  我不是什么中世纪拷问专家
Sorry. I'm not medieval torture expert guy.
他到底对你做了什么
What did he do to you, anyway?
和他做了什么无关
It's not about what he did.
而是我们完事之后他会做什么
It's about what he's going to do when we're done here,
也就是我想要让他做什么都行  和你一样
which is whatever I want him to, just like you.
比如  用这个刺穿他的身体
For example, drive this through his torso.
真是太疯狂了
That is crazy.
我不想这么做  但却做了
I didn't want to do it, but I did it, anyway.
这叫精神控制
It's called mind compulsion.
吸血鬼可以控制人类
Vampires can compel humans.
像我和我兄弟姐妹这样的始祖可以控制吸血鬼
Originals like my siblings and I can also compel vampires,
而没人能控制始祖
and no one can compel originals.
你懂了吗  很好
You following? Good.
那就是像你这样的全新的夜行吸血鬼
That is how a brand-new nightwalker such as yourself
为何在这里在谁都没察觉的情况下听从我的命令
is here doing my bidding with no one the wiser.
但是我的血液从来没流干过
But I never had my guts drained out of me.
是的  那个嘛  年轻的约书亚
Yes. That, young Joshua,
是因为在你体内没有一点马鞭草时
is because I got to you before you had even
我就已经控制你了
a drop of herbal vervain in your system.
马鞭草能阻止控制
You see, it prevents compulsion.
马塞尔让他所有的同伴
Marcel has had his whole crew
在我回来后开始饮用马鞭草
taking it since I returned to town,
那也就是为什么我们这位朋友需要放干血液
and that is why our friend here needs to be bled dry of it
那样我就能控制他听从我的命令了
so I can compel him to follow my every command,
现在我的哥哥被俘等待我的营救
and with my brother currently in captivity awaiting rescue,
我们就不能那么温柔了
we can't afford to be gentle about it.
不是吗
Can we?
真高兴你能来
Oh, so glad you could make it.
在你磨磨蹭蹭的时候
Elijah only lies daggered and rotting
以利亚身插匕首躺着腐烂呢
whilst you dillydally.
我能来你就该庆幸了
You're lucky I came at all.
你想要干嘛
What do you want?
昨晚海莉被马塞尔的人攻击了
Hayley was attacked last night by Marcel's crew
因为有人告诉他在法属区看到一只狼人
because somebody told him there was a werewolf in the quarter.
她只去过一个地方
She only made one stop.
不管是谁看到的她  出卖了她
Whoever saw her here ratted her out.
看好  学着点
Watch and learn.
-你好  索菲  -你好  凯蒂
- Hey, Soph. - Hey, Katie.
那里面都是金盏花
That's filled with marigold,
很能吸引异性
great for attracting the opposite sex,
很配你
Would look awesome on you.
深表怀疑
I very seriously doubt that.
你还有其他的吗  有...
Do you have any others, one with, say--
我不知道  也许是附子草
I don't know-- wolfsbane, perhaps?
附子草  你为什么想要那个
Wolfsbane? Why would you want that?
别跟我装傻
Please do not play dumb with me.
丽贝卡
Rebekah!
我只卖了一些药草给那个狼人  仅此而已
I just sold the werewolf some herbs. That's all.
你在骗我吗  凯蒂
Are you lying to me, Katie?
我建议你诚实回答我的问题
I suggest you answer my question honestly.
回答她的问题  凯蒂  拜托
Just answer the question, Katie, please.
是  我告诉别人了  但是你不理解
Yes. I told someone, but you don't understand.
我爱他
I--I love him.
告诉我  你的吸血鬼情人是谁
Then tell me, who is this vampire Romeo of yours?
要我倒数吗
Shall I count to 3?
快点
Be quick about it.
我还要建立一整个部队呢
I have an army to build,
一个被控制的仆从可不是一支部队
and one compelled minion does not an army make.
怎么样
Well?
你说对了谁是叛徒
You were right about the traitor.
幸运的是  她只是个孩子
Luckily, she's just a kid
对我们一无所知  也不知道我们的目的
and she doesn't know anything about us and what we're up to.
你想听听
Do you want to hear the part
最能让你高兴的事吗
that's gonna please you the most?
请说吧
Oh, do tell.
她爱着马塞尔的一个亲信
She's in love with someone in Marcel's inner circle.
猜猜是谁
Guess who it is.
左膀右臂  得力助手
Right-hand-man type, favors silly caps?
回答正确加两分
Two points for you.
蒂埃里和敌人越来越亲近了
Thierry is fraternizing with the enemy.
那就意味着他不知不觉
Well, that means he just unwittingly
变成了我们整个计划的关键
became the key to our entire plan.
我说了这能让你很高兴
I told you you'd be pleased.
在一个吸血鬼和女巫对峙的城市里
Oh, to be young and in love in a city
血气方刚  深陷热恋
where witches and vampires are at war.
真是太不幸了
How very tragic.
你疯了吗
Are you out of your mind?
-不行  -这很简单
- No way. - It's very simple.
我们只要你施一个小小的
We need you to perform a teeny,
非常小的定位咒帮我们找到我们的哥哥
tiny locator spell to help us find our brother.
在镇上任何使用魔法的女巫都会被抓
Witches who practice magic in this town get caught,
然后会被杀
and they get killed.
对  这事嘛
Yes. About that,
在我们交易时  似乎你遗漏了一个重要细节
it seems you left out a crucial detail when we made our deal--
马塞尔的秘密武器
Marcel's secret weapon,
他知道女巫使用魔法的办法
the way he knows when a witch is using magic.
这么高的小女孩  很可爱  很容易生气
Girl about yay high, cute as a button, anger issues.
达维娜
Davina?
你在哪看到她的
Where have you seen her?
不知道
I don't know.
那个小屁孩抹去了我的记忆
The little brat erased my memory
就在她用她该死的意念把我扔出窗外之后
right after she threw me out a window with her bloody mind.
我来说重点吧
Let me cut to the chase.
以利亚在达维娜手上
Davina has Elijah.
你们女巫  我想
You witches, I assume,
会很想把达维娜和马塞尔分开
want to get Davina away from Marcel.
我们不知道她在哪
We don't know where she is.
因此  我们需要魔法
Ergo, we need magic.
达维娜会感觉到的
Davina would sense it.
当然除非  另一个女巫
Unless, of course, another witch--
比如  因为一个叛徒
Say, a traitor to the cause,
比如凯蒂
Katie, for example--
同时在施一个更加强大的魔法
was to perform much more powerful magic at the same time.
那样就会产生一个烟雾
That would create a smokescreen
能够掩盖你的小小咒语不被达维娜发现
concealing your very small spell from Davina.
凯蒂不该死
Katie doesn't deserve to die.
索菲·德弗罗
Sophie Deveraux...
你不可能这么有原则
You're in no position to be so principled.
没有战略上的损失是不能赢得战争的
You can't win a war without a few strategic losses,
不管那损失会有多让人可惜
no matter how regrettable they may be.
有多少次吸血鬼总是领先一步
How many times have the vampires been one step ahead,
知道一些他们不该知道的事情
known something they shouldn't,
你的姐姐在公共广场被处决
your sister executed in the public square
就因为使用魔法  谁先知道她会被抓住
for practicing magic who knew she'd be caught?
她有没有试图逃走
Did she even attempt to flee?
她藏在一艘货船的货舱里
She was caught hiding in a cargo hold of a freighter
就在船准备在密西西比河里起航时被抓了
before it set sail down the Mississippi.
那么是谁  请你告诉我
And who, pray tell,
在马塞尔的最重要亲信中
in Marcel's valued inner circle
管理他的码头生意
manages his business at the docks?
凯蒂的男朋友  蒂埃里
Katie's boyfriend Thierry.
你说得对  他很不错
You're right. He's good.
对吧  我叫他音乐人
Right? Music man I call him.
女士们都爱他  但是他心有所属了
Ladies love him, but he's spoken for.
他总是围绕着他美丽的小女巫
He knocks around with this pretty, little witch,
说他爱她  但是我不知道
says he loves her, but I don't know.
你最重要的战士和你的敌人
Your brightest soldier is fraternizing
情谊深厚  你却不在意
with your enemy, and you don't care.
我当然在意  但是蒂埃里是个成熟男人了
Well, of course I care, but Thierry is a grown man.
他会自己做决定
He makes his own choices,
我也能得到一些重要内情
and I get some good intel.
再说了  他也不会做什么
Besides, he's not gonna do anything
危害我们事业的事情
to jeopardize what we're doing here.
你瞧瞧
I mean, check this out,
一个吸血鬼主持着一个奢华的慈善晚会
a vampire hosting a ritzy charity event.
我们在这里是一个整体  没人会破坏
We have a community here. No one is gonna mess that up.
不过呢
Still...
你还是不会想让那些女巫们太大胆了
You don't want the witches to get too bold,
考虑到一个女巫说镇上有狼人
given that a witch's tip about a werewolf in town
导致了你的夜行吸血鬼的失踪
led to the disappearance of your nightwalkers.
我确定你考虑了
I'm sure you've considered
这可能是个陷阱的可能性
the possibility that it could've been a trap.
也许我该给点暗示了
Maybe I'll send a little message.
蒂埃里
Thierry...
今晚带一队夜行吸血鬼去女巫那
Take a team of nightwalkers to the cauldron tonight,
小小的骚扰一下
do a little rousting...
蒂埃里  不用太客气了
Oh, and, Thierry, make it nasty.
于是然后
And so with that,
我搬回这里为了更亲近我的哥哥们  因为
I moved back here to be closer to my brothers because--
实话实说吧  家人最重要了  对吧  卡米尔
let's face it-- family is important, right, Camille?
叫我卡米  我得改掉这个胸牌
Cami. I have to change this name tag.
喝醉了的人都喜欢用法语跟我搭讪
Drunk guys keep hitting on me in French.
你真的以前没来过这里吗
You sure you haven't been in here before?
你看起来很面熟
Your face looks so familiar.
你一定是见过我在外面走过吧
You must have seen me out and about.
你不是在和马塞尔·杰拉德约会吗
Aren't you dating Marcel Gerard?
他是我的朋友  算是吧
He's a pal of mine... sort of.
我听说他在卢梭时期就喜欢金发的酒保了
I heard he had a crush on the blond bartender at Rousseau's.
我不会管那叫约会
I would hardly call it dating.
他在追求我  算是吧
He's wooing me... sort of.
我不知道
I don't know.
他很有魅力
He's very charming,
这大概意味着我该赶快逃走
which probably means I should run for the hills.
我自己现在有点处在分分合合的状态中
I'm kind of in an on-again/off-again thing myself at the moment.
这样最糟了  不是吗
Those are the worst, aren't they,
有些你放不下
the ones you can't shake,
虽然你不会上当
even though you know better,
你总是很明白
and you always know better?
我喜欢你  卡米
I like you, Cami.
大部分女孩都很烦地爱发牢骚
Most girls have the unfortunate tendency of being whiny,
嘲讽别人
little twits.
谢了
Thanks...I think.
我该去参加今晚这个慈善家举办的
Hey, I'm supposed to go to this posh charity thing
奢华的慈善晚会
thrown by this philanthropist tonight.
他有点像盖茨比  筹办了一个低劣的派对
He's a bit of a Gatsby, throws a mean party.
有兴趣吗
Any interest?
小妹
Little sister.
哥哥  我相信我确保了
Well, brother, I believe I've made certain
马塞尔今晚会有点分心
Marcel will be properly distracted tonight.
我该问吗
Dare I ask?
只能说他的注意力不会在我们身上
Let's just say his attention will not be on us.
我尽到了自己的绵薄之力
I did my bit.
你在忙什么来确保以利亚的平安回来
What are you doing to ensure Elijah's safe return?
现在呢  我在准备以防心肠软的做个保险
Currently, I'm preparing insurance against the tender-hearted.
什么意思
Meaning?
我们需要给凯蒂做个合适的动机
We need proper motivation for Katie
在今晚施个强大的咒语
to cast a powerful spell tonight.
我在制作动机呢
I'm creating that motivation.
马塞尔下令骚扰女巫
Marcel has ordered a rousting of the witches.
不
No!
我就反过来  安排事情悲剧地出错
I, in turn, have arranged for things to go tragically wrong.
明白要做什么吗
You understand what you're to do?
没问题
Good.
外面怎么了
What's happening out there?
是克劳斯
Oh, it's Klaus.
他让马塞尔觉得女巫
He's convinced Marcel that the witches
在计划采取行动对付他
are planning to make a move against him.
马塞尔想让我们来给个暗示
Marcel wants us to send a message,
如果他觉得我偏宠了
and if he thought I was playing favorites
就因为我爱上了一个女巫
just because I'm in love with a witch--
再说一次
Say that again.
我爱你  凯蒂
I love you, Katie,
一切都会好起来的  我保证
And all this is gonna be ok, promise.
马塞尔也许不在意
Marcel may not be concerned
蒂埃里那些你侬我侬
with Thierry's romantic entanglements.
那边我已经去过了
I already got that one.
但还有些罪过对他而言
But there are other crimes which he'll be
就不那么容易原谅了
less inclined to so easily forgive...
蒂埃里
Aah! Thierry! Aah!
放开她  滚开
Leave her alone. Get off.
杀死自己的同僚  就算一个
Killing a vampire, for example.
那将是不可原谅的
That would be unforgivable.
如果凯蒂想让她的爱人
If Katie hopes to save her one true love
免于马塞尔的惩罚
from Marcel's punishment,
而想要救他
well, a rescue mission
必须使用魔法
like that will require something positively magical,
不过话说回来
But then...
除了爱情还有什么值得付出生命呢
What's worth dying for if not love?
化妆舞会
造福全城
不得不赞一句  这个背景音乐
Well, it's certainly a fitting backdrop
很适合今晚
for tonight's events, I must say.
她在这里做什么
What's she doing here?
还有什么比让马塞尔的的人类小女友
What better way to distract Marcel
置身于吸血鬼扎堆的地方
than to put his very human,
更能分散他精力
new girl in a room chock full of vampires?
你好  亲爱的  你好美
Hello, darling. You look precious.
这个舞会真荒诞
This party is ridiculous,
但我觉得我会慢慢喜欢上它
but I think I could get to enjoy this place.
他就是那个臭名昭著的令人捉摸不定的家伙
Is he the infamous on-again/off-again?
实际上  你说的那个是哥哥
He's the brother, actually,
而我妹妹说得没错
and my sister is right.
你的确很美
You do look stunning.
你这身行头也很不错
You clean up pretty well yourself.
别被唬弄了  亲爱的
Well, don't be fooled, love.
我可是只披着羊皮的狼
I'm the devil in disguise.
你俩聊  我要来点酒
You two chitchat. I need booze.
-跳舞吗  -好的
- Shall we? - Ok.
苏格兰威士忌  谢谢
Scotch, please.
你邀请她来是想让自己招人喜欢吗
You're trying to be cute inviting her here?
我觉得她很珍贵
I think she's darling.
我敢说你爱的就是她那颗纯洁的心
I can tell you fancy her pure heart.
或许哪天我会亲手喂给你
Perhaps I'll feed it to you.
你吃醋的样子真好看  丽贝卡
Hmm, jealousy looks good on you, Rebekah.
丽贝卡说的那个人
The guy of hers Rebekah was talking about,
我觉得应该就是马塞尔
I'm sensing that would be Marcel.
要是我才不想那么多呢
I wouldn't worry about it.
多事老黄历了
Ancient history.
我在想的是你妹妹是个贱人
I'm beginning to think your sister is a bit of a bitch.
这个词儿好像还是她首创的
It's as though she invented the term.
听着
Listen.
允许我离开一下
Pardon me for a moment.
卡米
Cami.
杀手舞会
Hey, killer party.
这是应付公事的
Oh, it's more of a work thing.
我本打算邀请你...
I would've invited you...
没事  不过是约过一次会而已
Oh, no. We've been on one date.
不需要解释什么
No explanation necessary.
你做你的事  我会自娱自乐的
You do your thing. I'll entertain myself.
什么  弃你不顾
What, leave you alone,
看着你和别人一起
looking the way you do?
想都别想
Hell with that.
你不该到这里来的
You're not supposed to be out here.
你是谁
Who are you?
对不起  我没想吓着你
Sorry. I didn't mean to scare you.
我是萨宾  我们见过
I'm Sabine. We met.
我是索菲的朋友
I'm one of Sophie's friends.
你是这里的女巫
You're one of the witches.
索菲让我在大家
Sophie just asked me to come
都出去玩的时候过来陪你
keep you company while everyone is out.
它被你吸引了
You know, it's drawn to you.
你肚里的孩子
The child you're carrying
一半吸血鬼  一半狼人
is part vampire, part werewolf.
你和克劳斯创造了一个很特别的东西
You and Klaus made something special.
你说话口气像以利亚
You sound like Elijah.
他觉得这个孩子会给我们营造
He thinks this baby is gonna make us
一个欢乐的大家庭  但他现在却不在了
one big, happy family, but now he's gone,
还有...
And...
我甚至都不知道它究竟...
I don't even know what...
是什么
it is.
听着  如果你想得话我可以帮你
You know, I can do something about that if you want,
我是说  帮你知道它是男是女
I mean, find out if it's a boy or girl.
我还以为你们不能在这儿使用巫术
I thought you couldn't do witchy stuff around here.
这不是巫术  只是一个老把戏
It's not magic, just an old trick
我奶奶教我的
My grandmother taught me.
来吧
Come on.
你肯定有点好奇的
You have to be a little curious.
我记得你说你是做社区工作的
I thought you said you were in community work.
社区筹款
Community fundraising.
办派对  让人们打开钱包捐款
Throw a party, folks open their wallets.
我就是干这个的
It's kind of my thing.
我大概就是你们说的不好却必不可少的人[恶魔]
Guess I'm what you call a necessary evil.
那丽贝卡呢  她是你的捐款人之一吗
And Rebekah, she's one of your donors?
她是个老朋友
She's an old friend.
也不会太老
Can't be that old.
她看上去比我年轻
She looks younger than me.
你会大吃一惊的
You'd be surprised.
我遇见她的时候还是个孩子
I was a kid when I met her.
别再说她了
Enough about her.
我只是想跟你在一起
I just want to be right here with you.
你还真是个令人发指的小恶魔  是不是
You really are a hideously evil little thing, aren't you?
废话  他们两个是绝配
Nonsense. They're perfect for each other.
你想分马塞尔的心  这就成了
You wanted Marcel distracted. Voila.
我该走了
My cue to leave.
失陪
Excuse me.
你到底干了什么
What the hell did you do?
别在这儿说  换个地方说
Not here. No, not here.
我知道你觉得他是个禽兽
I know you think he's a monster.
我怎么想不重要
It doesn't matter what I think.
蒂埃里又杀了一个吸血鬼
Thierry killed another vampire.
他打破了马塞尔最重大的规矩
He broke Marcel's biggest rule.
你再也见不到他了
You'll never see him again...
除非我们做点什么
Unless we do something.
"我们"
"We"?
我想要救我的族人
I want to save our people.
你想救蒂埃里吗
You want to save Thierry?
要达到这两个目的只有一种方法
There's only one way we can do both.
准备好了吗
You ready?
马塞尔  要出事了
Marcel. Something is coming.
魔法
Magic.
我想听听你怎么说
I want to hear your side of it.
马塞尔  别这样
Hey, Marcel, come on.
你的版本  说
Your version. Go.
我们当时正在扔锅炉
We were tossing the cauldron.
那个人  某个夜行吸血鬼
This guy, some nightwalker,
无缘无故袭击了凯蒂
he attacked Katie for no reason.
他叫麦克斯  是我转化的
His name was Max. I turned him.
他并不需要什么原因
As far as reasons go, he doesn't need one.
她是个女巫  而他是个吸血鬼
She was a witch. He was a vampire.
现在他死了
Now he's dead.
我不是有意的
I didn't mean for it to happen.
你打破了我最重要的规矩
You broke my most important rule.
该死  我们做朋友多久了  七十年
Damn it, t. How long we been friends, 70 years?
是的
Yeah.
我把你变成了不死之身
I turned you into something that would never die.
我给了你一份礼物
I gave you a gift.
我对你也一直很忠诚
And I have been loyal to you all this time,
我现在依旧很忠诚
and I still am.
我依旧是你的朋友  马塞尔
I'm still your friend, Marcel.
我发誓  这没有变
I swear, that hasn't changed.
你说的对  亲爱的
You were right, love.
他脾气很大  不是吗
He's got a temper, doesn't he?
或许现在我该记起我早就知道会这样的
I guess this is the moment I remember I know better.
这是我们在他女人那里找到的
We found this at his girl's place.
还是我的朋友  是吗
Still my friend, huh?
真搞笑
That's funny because it looks to me
因为你的小女巫手里
like that little witch of yours got her hands on a spell
有我一直锁起来的咒语
that I keep locked away.
马塞尔  我从没见过这个
Marcel, I have never seen that.
闭嘴
Shut up.
我看你手上依旧戴着
I see on your hand, you still have
我给你的日光戒指
the daylight ring I gave you.
你还要制作戒指的秘方干什么
So what would you need with the recipe for making new ones?
除非你准备背叛我
Unless maybe you and Katie were gonna go off
和凯蒂一起另立门户
and start a little kingdom of your own?
不是的  马塞尔
Marcel, no.
让我教教你什么是朋友
Here's a lesson in friendship.
朋友不会欺骗我  违反我的规矩
Friends don't lie to me, they don't break my rules,
更不会偷走属于我的东西
and they do not steal what is mine.
鉴于其谋杀同伴的罪行
For the crime of murdering one of his own,
我宣判将蒂埃里·范舒囚禁于花园100年
I sentence Thierry Vanchure to 100 years in the garden.
好戏上演了
And it begins.
你的决定是正确的
You're doing the right thing.
这是唯一能找到以利亚的方式
It's the only way to find Elijah.
我只是做我该做的
I'm doing what I have to do.
不要  凯蒂
Katie, no!
出现得正是时候
Like clockwork.
快点
Hurry.
不
No!
你来拯救自己的男人吗
You're here to save your man.
放马过来吧  小姑娘
Well, come on, little girl.
去死吧  你这个贱人
Die, you son of a bitch.
不要  凯蒂
No! Katie!
事情不对劲
Something's wrong.
凯蒂的魔法停止了
Katie's magic stopped.
我可以继续
I can keep going.
不行  她会察觉的
You can't. She'll sense it.
我可以找到达维娜  再给我一点时间
No. I can find Davina. I just need another moment.
你或许可以为了夺回你的女巫奋不顾身
You may be willing to die to get your witch back,
但海莉和孩子会跟着你送死
but Hayley and the baby will die with you.
以利亚永远不会原谅我们
Elijah will never forgive us,
救回他也变会得毫无意义
and rescuing him will be for nothing.
都结束了  我们失败了
It's over. We failed.
不  凯蒂  不不不
No. Katie. No, no, no, no.
不
No.
告诉我
Just tell me this.
她值得吗
Was she worth it?
我爱他
I loved her.
把他封起来
Seal him up
让他在这腐烂
And let him rot.
凯米看见了多少
How much did Cami see?
她只见到了一场争执  伙计
She just saw an argument, mate.
没什么你应付不来的
It's nothing you can't fix.
你真的很喜欢她  是吗
You really like her, don't you?
我喜欢她没有被牵扯进这一切的样子
I like that she's not a part of any of this.
有时用人类的视角看看这个世界
Sometimes it's good to see the world
也是一件好事
the way the humans do.
蒂埃里的事我很抱歉
I am sorry about Thierry, you know?
看得出他是你很好的朋友
I can tell he was a good friend.
是我一手打造了他
I made him what he was.
显然  我不该信任他
Obviously, my trust was misplaced.
这也不会好过一点
Doesn't make it easier.
你今晚救了我  我欠你份人情
You saved me tonight. I guess I owe you one.
你想要回你的哥哥
You asked for your brother back.
这是我唯一能为你做的了
Seems like the least I can do.
-凯米  -想都别想
- Cami.  - Don't even try it.
我知道你为什么来
I get the bro code.
你是来为你朋友说好话的
You're here to smooth things over for your friend.
你是个好人  但是...
It's very nice of you, but--
但你曾被伤害过
But you've been hurt before,
你不敢再轻易尝试
and you aren't taking any more chances.
诸如此类的
Something like that.
今晚我见到的他
The guy I saw tonight,
不是我想象中的他
not the guy I thought he was.
如果他能轻易就这样发怒...
And if he can turn on a dime like that--
听上去不止是普通的心碎
Sounds like more than just a broken heart.
看来有人背叛了你的信任
Someone broke your trust...
勇敢的酒保  卡米尔
Camille, the brave bartender.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry...
但我希望你能再给马塞尔一次机会
But I need you to give Marcel another chance.
看来是我会错意了
Wow. I totally misread that.
不  你看的很准
No. You read it quite well,
但我们都有自己的角色要扮演
But we all have our roles to play.
你去见了马塞尔  与他共舞
You went to Marcel's. You danced.
你为他与朋友争执感到难过
You feel badly that he had a row with his friend,
但除此以外  你只记得他很完美
But otherwise, all you remember is that it was perfect.
今晚真是彻底的失败
Well, tonight was an epic failure.
恰恰相反  妹妹
On the contrary, sister.
今晚成功极了
Tonight was a masterpiece.
你疯了吗
Are you mad?
凯蒂在索菲完成咒语前死了
Katie died before Sophie could complete the spell.
我很清楚  我杀了凯蒂
Oh, I'm well aware. I killed Katie.
你干了什么
You what?
我们寻死的小女巫没理由
There's no way our little suicide witch
不试图让马塞尔和她陪葬
wasn't gonna try and take out Marcel with her.
我救了他的命  正因如此
I saved his life, and in doing so,
他正遂我愿
I now have him exactly where I want him.
索菲信任你
Sophie trusted you.
我信任你  而不是我更靠谱的本能
I trusted you against all my better instincts.
醒醒吧  丽贝卡
Wake up, Rebekah.
女巫们只为她们自己谋划
The witches are on no one's side but their own.
她们只想得到达维娜这个姑娘
This girl Davina, that's all they want,
当她们拥有了她  你觉得会怎样
and when they have her, what do you think happens then?
休战吗  当然不是
A truce? Of course not.
他们会用达维娜的力量对抗我们所有人
They will use Davina's power against all of us.
即便你说得对  计划是找到以利亚
Even if you're right, the plan was to find Elijah,
而你让我们失望了
and you failed us.
你总对我缺乏信心
You always did lack faith.
由于保护马塞尔  他更信任我了
By protecting Marcel, I've cemented his trust,
信任到他同意把以利亚还给我们
so much so that he's agreed to return Elijah to us.
时机一到
And when the time is right,
等他告诉了我达维娜所有的事
when he has told me everything I need to know about Davina,
我要亲自掌控她
I will have her for myself.
我毫不怀疑
I have all the faith in the world
你能心想事成  尼克
that you'll get what you want, Nik.
你一直如此
You always do,
不管我们其他人付出的代价
no matter what it costs the rest of us.
你让我恶心
You disgust me.
你还好吗  我很担心
Are you ok? I was so worried.
谢谢
Thank you.
我感觉到了你所做的一切
Whatever you did, I felt it.
你帮助了我
You helped me.
是那些老家伙  对吗
It was the old ones, wasn't it?
其实克劳斯是今晚救我的人
Actually, Klaus is the one that saved me tonight.
我要纠正错误
I'm gonna make things right,
从归还他的哥哥开始
starting off by giving him his brother back.
不行
No.
怎么了
What?
-达维娜  -不行
- Davina. - No.
你说过那帮老家伙很危险
You said the old ones were dangerous.
得知如何杀死他们前我不会归还他
I won't give him back until I know how to kill them.
我觉得你可能想知道
I thought you might like to know,
以利亚要回来了
Elijah is returning to us.
恭喜
Congratulations.
我想作恶多端也有好处
I guess being diabolical has its perks.
你不了解他  但你却想念他
You hardly know him, and yet you miss him.
我的哥哥为何
What is it about my brother
总能引人敬佩
that always inspires such instant admiration?
他对我很好
He was kind to me.
有时我会怀疑
There are moments when I doubt
我的家族能否得到救赎
if my family is capable of redemption...
我今天知道一件事
Hey, I learned something today.
我觉得是个女孩
I think it's a girl.
但每当我想放弃时
Yet each time that I am tempted to surrender,
我看到一丝善良
I see it, the glimmer of goodness
让我相信救赎
that allows me to believe.
圣彼得街
你在跟踪我
You're following me.
也许是你挡了我的路
Maybe you're just in my way.
我告诉过你这帮罪恶的盟友
I told you no good would come
不会带来好处
from this unholy alliance of yours.
至少我有所作为
At least I'm doing something.
你呢
What about you?
萨宾  告诉他们你看到的
Sabine, tell them what you saw.
是那个狼人姑娘
It's the girl, the wolf.
我觉得是个女孩
I think it's a girl.
不  等等
No. Wait.
等什么
Wait what?
快告诉我这不是个小克劳斯
Please tell me I'm not having a mini Klaus.
[咒语]
Hoc est infantima malom.
Nos omnia perdetu el eam.
[咒语]
Hoc est infantima malom.
Nos omnia perdetu el eam.
无搜索结果